Finding Aid for Constance E. Cumbey papers, 1920-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Group 2
    - Music Therapy (Box 54)
    - Rosalind Musselman (Box 54)
    - Mystical Rose, New Age Tools and Toys (Box 54)
    - Mysticism (Box 54)
    - Ralph Nader / Public Citizen (Box 54)
    - John Nesbitt (Box 54)
    - Naropa Institute (Box 54)
    - Narrow Way Ministries (Box 54)
    - National Association of Evangelicals (Box 54)
    - National Association of Social Workers (Box 54)
    - National Association of Neighborhood Schools, Inc. (Box 54)
    - National Catholic Education Association (Box 54)
    - National Catholic Education Association, Resource Packet and 1985 Preliminary Program and Program (Box 54)
    - National Catholic Reporter (Box 54)
    - National Center for Privatization (Box 54)
    - National Commodity and Barter Association (NCBA) (Box 54)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 54)
    - National Council of Churches (incl. items concerning homosexuality) (Box 54)
    - National Council of Churches in the USA (Box 54)
    - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 54)
    - National Day of Prayer (Box 54)
    - National Diffusion Network (Box 55)
    - National Education Association (NEA) (Box 55)
    - National Education Association, "Issues in Human Relations Training," 1962 (Box 55)
    - National Identity Card (Box 55)
    - National Humanities Center (Box 55)
    - National Federation for Decency (Box 55)
    - National Leadership Conference (Box 55)
    - National Organization for an American Revolution (N.O.A.R.) (Box 55)
    - National Organization of Women (NOW) (Box 55)
    - National Association of Religious Broadcasters, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Native American Spiritualities (Box 55)
    - National Prayer Day for Israel (Box 55)
    - National Public Referendum (Box 55)
    - National World Prayer (Box 55)
    - The Nature Conservancy (Box 55)
    - Naturopathy (Box 55)
    - The Navigators (Box 55)
    - Nazism, 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Near Death Experiences (Box 55)
    - Nebraska (Box 55)
    - Neo-nazi (Box 55)
    - Neopaganism (Box 55)
    - Neopentecostalism [Pentecostal], 4 folders (Box 55)
    - Neopentecostal Booklets, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Network, A Catholic Social Justice Lobby (Box 56)
    - Networking (Box 56)
    - Networks, Miscellaneous (Box 56)
    - The Networking Institute, Inc. (Box 56)
    - Nevada (Box 56)
    - New Age Activists (Box 56)
    - New Age Style Advertising (Box 56)
    - New Age Art (Box 56)
    - New Age Calendar (Box 56)
    - New Age Computer Network (Box 56)
    - New Age Fairs (Box 56)
    - New Age Financing (Box 56)
    - New Age Fundraisers (Box 56)
    - New Age Journal (Box 56)
    - New Age Library (Box 56)
    - New Age Mailing Lists (NAM) (Box 56)
    - New Age / Metaphysical Booksellers (Box 56)
    - New Age Literature, Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 57)
    - New Age Military, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - New Age Movement, Articles On (Box 57)
    - New Age Music, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - New Age Opposition (Box 57)
    - New Age Organizations (Box 57)
    - New Age Publishers (Box 57)
    - New Age Outreach (Box 57)
    - New Age Politicians (Box 57)
    - New Age Politics (Box 57)
    - New Age Movement Prophecy (Box 57)
    - New Age Singles Activities (Box 57)
    - New Age Source (Box 57)
    - New Age Unconverted (Box 57)
    - New Age Weaponry (Box 57)
    - New Beginnings Fellowship (Box 58)
    - New Constitution of USA (Box 58)
    - New Creation Worldwide Cruises (Box 58)
    - New Dimensions Radio Network (Box 58)
    - New Group of World Servers (Box 58)
    - New Jersey (Box 58)
    - New Mexico (Box 58)
    - New Mexico, Education (Box 58)
    - New Thought Religion (Box 58)
    - "New Wave Theology," by Rev. Robert Crabtree, M.A. (Box 58)
    - New World Alliance (Box 58)
    - New Word Religion (Box 58)
    - New World Order (Box 58)
    - New York (Box 58)
    - New York Times (Box 58)
    - Nilgiri Press (Box 58)
    - Nirvana (Box 58)
    - Nityanada Institute (Box 58)
    - Oguchi Nkowocha, M.D. The Comforter (Box 58)
    - 1982 Prophecies, Dr. Joan Bownie (Box 58)
    - North Carolina (Box 58)
    - North Dakota (Box 58)
    - Gary North, 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Gary North, "Megatrends" (Box 58)
    - North South Commission (Box 58)
    - Norway (Box 58)
    - Nuclear Times (Box 58)
    - Nudist Colonies (Box 58)
    - Numerology (Box 58)
    - New Right Political Movement (Box 59)
    - New Species Beliefs (Box 59)
    - Nutrifoods (Box 59)
    - Nutritionists (Box 59)
    - Nutripathy, American College of (Box 59)
    - Oasis Center for Human Potential (Box 59)
    - Oakland County Bible Students (Box 59)
    - Occult Organization List (Box 59)
    - Occult Revival (Box 59)
    - Occultism (Box 59)
    - Occultism: Christian Tactics Against (Box 59)
    - October Newsletter (Box 59)
    - Octology (Box 59)
    - Ohio, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Oil (Box 59)
    - Ohio, Columbus (Box 59)
    - Oklahoma (Box 59)
    - Oklahoma, Oklahoma City (Box 59)
    - Omega Institute for Holistic Studies (Box 59)
    - Omegan (Box 59)
    - Omni Publications (Box 59)
    - One, Inc. Seminars (Box 59)
    - One World (Box 59)
    - "Orage and The New Age Circle," by Paul Selver (Box 59)
    - Oregon (Box 59)
    - Oregon, Education (Box 59)
    - Oregon, Eugene (Box 60)
    - Oregon, Portland, 4 folders (Box 60)
    - Oregon, Salem (Box 60)
    - Organized Crime Links (Box 60)
    - The Other Side (Box 60)
    - Ourobourus Institute (Box 60)
    - Pacific Institute, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Padre Pio (Box 60)
    - Paganism (Box 60)
    - Paideia Proposal (Box 60)
    - Thomas Paine (Box 60)
    - Martin Palmer (Box 60)
    - Pantheism (Box 60)
    - Parabola (Box 60)
    - Parapsychology (Box 60)
    - Parental Rights Legislation, Parental Rights (Box 60)
    - Parenting (Box 60)
    - Parliament of Religions (Box 60)
    - Jonathan Parker, Institute of Human Development (Box 60)
    - "PATRIOT" Movement (Box 60)
    - Patterson Strategy Letter (Box 60)
    - Linus Paulding (Box 60)
    - Paulist Press (Box 60)
    - Earl Paulk, 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Pax Christi (Box 61)
    - Peace (Box 61)
    - Peace Academy (Box 61)
    - Peace Child Foundation (Box 61)
    - Peace On Earth, The Kingdom Congress (Box 61)
    - Peace Movement (Box 61)
    - Peace Net (Box 61)
    - Peacequake '82 (Box 61)
    - Peace Ribbon Project (Box 61)
    - Dennis Peacocke (Box 61)
    - Norman Vincent Peale (Box 61)
    - Joseph Chilton Pearce (Box 61)
    - M. Scott Peck (Box 61)
    - J.C. Penney (Box 61)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 61)
    - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia (Box 61)
    - Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh (Box 61)
    - Pentecostal Oneness Movement, "Think It Not Strange," by Fred J. Foster (Box 61)
    - People For The American Way (Box 61)
    - Fr. Eduard Perrone (Box 61)
    - Personal Freedom Outreach (Box 61)
    - Phenomenews (Box 61)
    - Phil Phillips (Box 61)
    - The Philosophical Research Society (Box 61)
    - Photographs (miscellaneous) (Box 61)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 61)
    - Pineal Gland Theories (Box 61)
    - The Plan, "Hierarchy and The Plan" (Box 61)
    - Planetary Initiative, Planetary Citizens, etc., 5 folders (Box 61)
    - Planet-Drum Foundation (Box 61)
    - Playboy Philosophies (Box 61)
    - P.P.B.E.S. (Planning -- Programming -- Budgeting -- Evaluating -- Systems) (Box 61)
    - Ministry Registration (Box 61)
    - Polarity Therapies (Box 61)
    - Political Networking (Box 61)
    - Pope John Paul II, 4 folders (Box 62)
    - Pope Paul VI (Box 62)
    - Population Control (Box 62)
    - Populist Party (Box 62)
    - Pornography (Box 62)
    - Portland Bible Temple (Box 62)
    - Positive Mental Attitude (Box 62)
    - Posse Comitatus (Box 62)
    - Potentials Unlimited Tapes (Box 62)
    - Ezra Pound (Box 62)
    - Ezra Pound, Hindu -- Occult-Vortex (Box 62)
    - Ezra Pound, Social Credit Movement (Box 62)
    - Ezra Pound, Vorticism (Box 62)
    - Ezra Pound, Ephemeral Materials (Box 62)
    - Prayer (Box 62)
    - Prayer In Schools Issue (Box 62)
    - Presbyterian Church (Box 62)
    - Derek Prince (Box 62)
    - Prison-Ashram Project (Box 62)
    - Prison Networking Projects (Box 62)
    - Privatization (Box 62)
    - The Process Church of the Final Judgment (Box 62)
    - Proctor & Gamble (Box 62)
    - Pro Family Forum Alert [and The Family Educator] (Box 62)
    - Project Mozart (Box 62)
    - Prophecies (Misc. Christian), 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Prophesy Newsletter (Box 62)
    - Elizabeth Clare Prophet (Box 63)
    - Protocols of The Learned Elders of Zion (Box 63)
    - Ira Progroff Workshops (Box 63)
    - Prophecy In The News (Box 63)
    - Prosperity Teachings (Box 63)
    - Prosperos Rectory (Box 63)
    - Protestant Apostasy (Box 63)
    - Prout International (Box 63)
    - Proutist Universal (Box 63)
    - PSI Training (Box 63)
    - PSI Training, "Living Synergistically" by Thomas D. Willhite, and "My Glory and the Lifter of My Head," by Ronald D. Willhite (Box 63)
    - PSI Training, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - The Psychic Eye (Box 63)
    - Psychics, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Psychologists' Support (Box 63)
    - Psychotechnologies (Misc.) (Box 63)
    - Psychotronics (Box 63)
    - PTL Television Network [Jim and Tammy Faye Bakker] (incl. two vinyl records, correspondence with Jim Bakker) (Box 63)
    - Publishers (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Pat Pulling (Dungeons & Dragons) (Box 63)
    - Eldon Purvis, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Pyramidology (Box 63)
    - Pyramidology, "The House of Glory. An interpretation and elucidation of the radian prophecies, and allied messages of the Holy Bible and the Great Pyramid at Gizeh," by Worth Smith (Box 63)
    - Quakers (Box 63)
    - Quartus (Box 63)
    - Quest Educational Program (Box 63)
    - Carol Quigley (Box 63)
    - Rabi Rabindranath R. Maharaj (Box 64)
    - Racism (Box 64)
    - Radar (Box 64)
    - Radiation Scares (Box 64)
    - Rainbows (Box 64)
    - The Rainbow Group (Box 64)
    - Rama (Box 64)
    - Ram Das (Box 64)
    - Ramtha (Box 64)
    - The Gary Randall Program (Box 64)
    - Lyle J. Rapacki (Box 64)
    - Rapture Theories (Box 64)
    - Carl Raschke (Box 64)
    - Reader's Digest (Box 64)
    - Ronald Reagan (Box 64)
    - Rebirthing (Box 64)
    - Reconstructionalism (Box 64)
    - Reflexology (Box 64)
    - Reformation Study Center (Box 64)
    - Refugee Issues (Box 64)
    - Regionalism (Box 64)
    - Wilhelm Reich (Box 64)
    - Reiki (Box 64)
    - Reincarnation (Box 64)
    - Mary Stewart Relfe (Box 64)
    - Religious Heritage of America (Box 64)
    - Reorganized Latter Day Saints (RLDS) (Box 64)
    - Renew Programs (Box 64)
    - Renew Programs, "renew Leadership Handbook" (Box 64)
    - Research Studies (Box 64)
    - Restoration Revival Movement (Box 64)
    - Restoration Revival Movement, "The Walk" by John Robert Stevens (Box 64)
    - Revision Magazine (Box 65)
    - Revolution Books (Box 65)
    - Right To Die Movement (Box 65)
    - Right To Life Movement (Box 65)
    - Jeremy Rifkin (Box 65)
    - Ritualistic Abuse (Box 65)
    - Alberto Riviera (Box 65)
    - Riverside Church, New York City (Box 65)
    - Oral Roberts (Box 65)
    - Pat Robertson
      - Pat Robertson (General) (Box 65)
      - Abortion (Box 65)
      - Articles (Box 65)
      - Books (Box 65)
      - Cartoons (Box 65)
      - Cashless Society / Economic and Social Views (Box 65)
      - Catholicism (Box 65)
      - Christian Booksellers Association (Box 65)
      - CBN Television Network (Box 65)
      - CBN Counseling Handbook for Telephone and Personal Ministry (Box 65)
      - CBN University (Box 65)
      - Children's Book (Box 65)
      - Congressional Meeting (Box 65)
      - Controversies (Box 65)
      - Correspondence with (Box 65)
      - Benjamin Creme Connections (Box 65)
      - Crystal Connection (Box 65)
      - Constance Cumbey Notes (Box 65)
      - Detroit Free Press article (Box 65)
      - "Don't Ask Me, Ask God," by Pat Robertson (Box 65)
      - Foreign Relations (Box 65)
      - J. Peter Grace (Box 65)
      - Hillsdale College (Box 65)
      - Jewish Views (Box 65)
      - Kingdom Theology (Box 65)
      - Legal Matters (Box 65)
      - London School of Economics (Box 65)
      - Marantha Connections (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
      - National Legal Foundation (Box 65)
      - National Perspective Institute (Box 65)
      - National Religious Broadcasters (Box 65)
      - Nazism (Box 66)
      - New Republic (Box 66)
      - Gary North's Views (Box 66)
      - Religious Freedom (Box 66)
      - Dede Robertson (Box 66)
      - Robertson In error (Box 66)
      - Pat Robertson's Perspective (Box 66)
      - Pat Robertson "Thick Packet" (Box 66)
      - Robertson's Views on Arms (Box 66)
      - 700 Club (Box 66)
      - Denita Soderman (Box 66)
      - Jimmy Swaggart Statement (Box 66)
      - Robert Tilton (Box 66)
      - Cornelius Van DerBreggen, Jr. (Box 66)
    - James Robison (Box 66)
    - Rock Church (Box 66)
    - Rockefellers (Box 66)
    - Rock Music (Box 66)
    - Rockford Institute (Box 66)
    - Nicholas Roerich (Box 66)
    - Rodale Enterprises (Box 66)
    - John Roger (Box 66)
    - Roman Catholic Apostasy, 3 folders (Box 66)
    - Roman Catholic Church: International Council of the Pontifical Council for Culture (Box 66)
    - Dr. Rodney Romney, Pr. 1st Baptist Church, Seattle (Box 66)
    - Rosicrucianism (Box 66)
    - Rotary Club (Box 66)
    - The Roundtable (Box 66)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul (Box 66)
    - Fr. Albert S. Roux (Box 66)
    - Edward H. Rowe (Box 66)
    - Mary Royer (Box 66)
    - Ilana Rubenfeld (Box 66)
    - Runes (Box 66)
    - Rushdony (Box 66)
    - Russia (Box 67)
    - Rutherford (Box 67)
    - Carl Sagan (Box 67)
    - Steven A. Samson, "Crossed Swords: Entanglements Between Church and State In America" (Box 67)
    - Sanat Kumara (Box 67)
    - John & Paula Sanford (Box 67)
    - Margaret Sanger (Box 67)
    - Satanism (Box 67)
    - Sant Thakar Singh (Box 67)
    - Satellite Technology (Box 67)
    - Mark Satin (incl. New Options), 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Frankie Schaeffer (Box 67)
    - Phyllis Schlafly (Box 67)
    - M. Basilea Schlink (Box 67)
    - Scholastic Book Services (Box 67)
    - School of Metaphysics (Box 67)
    - School of the Prophets (Box 67)
    - Robert Schuller (Box 67)
    - Fred Schulte (Box 67)
    - The Scientific and Medical Network (Box 67)
    - Scientists (Box 67)
    - Scientology (Box 67)
    - Scott (Chako Association) (Box 67)
    - Dr. Scott (Box 67)
    - Scouting (Box 67)
    - The Sealing Commission (Box 67)
    - David Seamands (Box 67)
    - The Seattle Times (Box 67)
    - Robert Seiple (Box 67)
    - Self-Esteem (Box 67)
    - Self-Realization Fellowship (Box 67)
    - Trip Seman (Box 67)
    - Senior Citizen Projects (Box 67)
    - Sensitivity Training (Box 67)
    - Seminary Infiltration (Box 67)
    - Seventh Day Adventists (Box 67)
    - Seventh Day Adventists (cont.) (Box 68)
    - Sex Education (Box 68)
    - Idries Shah (Box 68)
    - Shamanism (Box 68)
    - Shambala Publications (Box 68)
    - Shambala Training (Box 68)
    - Randy Shankle (Box 68)
    - Share International (Box 68)
    - Steve Shearer (Box 68)
    - Shepherding (Box 68)
    - Harold Sherman (Box 68)
    - Florence Scovel Shinn, "The Game of Life and How To Play It" (Box 68)
    - Shroud of Turin (Box 68)
    - Ronald J. Sider (Box 68)
    - Sierra Club (Box 68)
    - Signs And Wonders Ministries (Box 68)
    - Sikhism (Box 68)
    - Everett Sileven (incl. "The Christian and the Income Tax), 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Silva Mind Control (Box 68)
    - Dr. Robert L. Simonds, "As the Twig is Bent, A Parents Manual. Citizens for Excellence in Education" (Box 68)
    - Charles Simpson (Box 68)
    - Tom Sine (Box 68)
    - Singles Activities (Box 68)
    - Sister Monica (Box 68)
    - 666 Symbols (Box 68)
    - Sitara Foundation (Box 69)
    - Skinhead Movement (Box 69)
    - B.F. Skinner (Box 69)
    - Cleon Skousen (Box 69)
    - Malcolm Smith (Box 69)
    - Chuck Smith (Box 69)
    - Samantha Smith, New Awareness Consultants (Box 69)
    - Social Credit (Box 69)
    - Social Investment Series (Box 69)
    - Socialism (Box 69)
    - Social Security (Box 69)
    - Society of Universal Love (S.O.U.L.) (Box 69)
    - Society for World Peace (Box 69)
    - Sojourners Fellowship, 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Alexander Solzhenitsyn (Box 69)
    - Sonship (Box 69)
    - Sons of Liberty (Box 69)
    - The Soundworks, Inc. (Box 69)
    - Sources (Box 69)
    - Source Publications (Box 69)
    - South Africa (Box 69)
    - South Carolina (Box 69)
    - South Dakota (Box 69)
    - Southwest Radio Church (Box 69)
    - Southern Baptist Convention (Box 69)
    - Soviet-American Dialogue (Box 69)
    - Soviet Union (Box 69)
    - David Spangler, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - David Spangler Meeting Notes (Box 69)
    - S.P.C.K. (Box 69)
    - Spielberg (Box 69)
    - Spiral Report, Spiral Feedback [Society for the Protection of Individual Rights and Liberties] (Box 69)
    - Spirals (Box 69)
    - Spiritual Communism (Box 69)
    - Spiritual Counterfeits Project, 4 folders (Box 70)
    - Spiritual Frontiers Fellowship (Box 70)
    - Spiritual Unity of Nations (S.U.N.) (Box 70)
    - Spiritualists (Box 70)
    - Benjamin Spock, M.D. (Box 70)
    - Sports (Box 70)
    - Spotlight Magazine (Box 70)
    - R.C. Sproul (Box 70)
    - Sri Aurobindo Ashram Trust, "Flame of White Light" by T. V. Kapalisastry (Box 70)
    - Sri Chinmoy (Box 70)
    - "Stamp Out The New Age!" (Box 70)
    - Stanford Research Institute (Box 70)
    - Stanford University (Box 70)
    - The Stanley Foundation (Box 70)
    - Alan Stang (Box 70)
    - Starhawk (Box 70)
    - Marian Starnes (Box 70)
    - SUNY (State University of New York) (Box 70)
    - Betty St. Clair (Box 70)
    - The Stelle Group, 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Martha Jean Steinberg (Martha Jean the Queen) (Box 70)
    - Rudolf Steiner (Box 70)
    - Stephen Ministries, St. Louis, MO. (Box 71)
    - Stillpoint Press (Box 71)
    - Stock Market (Box 71)
    - W. Clement Stone (Box 71)
    - Stonehenge (Box 71)
    - Stress Control (Box 71)
    - Student Papers Regarding New Age Movement (Box 71)
    - Subliminal Messages (Box 71)
    - Subud (Box 71)
    - Sufism (Box 71)
    - Suicide (Box 71)
    - Superlearning (Box 71)
    - Survivalist Cults (Box 71)
    - Sutphen (Dick, Tranna, Tara, et al) (incl. Self Help Update) (Box 71)
    - Anthony G. Sutton (Box 71)
    - Jimmy Swaggart (Box 71)
    - Swami Radha (Box 71)
    - Swastikas (Box 71)
    - Swedenborgianism (Box 71)
    - Switzerland (Box 71)
    - Syda Foundation Ashrmas (Box 71)
    - Symbols (Box 71)
    - Synthesis Fellowship, Kansas City, MO. (Box 71)
    - Taize Ecumenical Community (Box 71)
    - Tantra Productions (Box 71)
    - Tarot Reading (Box 71)
    - Tarrytown Group (Box 71)
    - Tax (Box 71)
    - Tax Reform Movement, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Dr. Charles Taylor (Box 71)
    - Teilhard DeChardin (Box 72)
    - Television (Box 72)
    - Temple Mont Foundation (Box 72)
    - Temple of Set, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Templeton Prize (Box 72)
    - Ten Commandments (Box 72)
    - Tennessee (Box 72)
    - Terrorism (Box 72)
    - Tesla Physics (Box 72)
    - Testimonies (Box 72)
    - Texas, 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Texas, Dallas (incl. photographs) (Box 72)
    - Texas, Houston (Box 72)
    - "The Day After" (Box 72)
    - "The Last Temptation of Christ" (Box 72)
    - Robert Theobald (Box 72)
    - Theofile Society (Box 72)
    - Theosophical Society (Box 72)
    - Theosophical Society, leaflets and booklets, incl. The American Theosophist. (Box 72)
    - Theotherapy (Box 72)
    - Robert Thibodeau (Box 72)
    - Thomas Nelson Publishers (Box 72)
    - Tibetan Buddhism (Box 72)
    - Robert Tilton (Box 72)
    - Time-Life Books (Box 72)
    - John Todd (Box 72)
    - Penny Torres (Box 72)
    - Toys (Box 72)
    - Tracts (Christian) regarding the New Age Movement (Box 72)
    - Transcendental Meditation, 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Transcendental Mediation, Publications (incl. Maharishi International University) (Box 73)
    - Transformation 2000 Network Plan (Plexus Dir.; Aoarangi University; Media Foundation; I.C.C.; Village 2000 TAV 2000) (Box 73)
    - Transpersonal Psychology (Box 73)
    - Triangles (Box 73)
    - Tribulation (Box 73)
    - Tridentive Mass Cults (Box 73)
    - Trilateral Commission [Conspiracy Theories] (Box 73)
    - Trilateral Commission, "The Conspiracy Behind the Trilateral Commission," by the Executive Intelligence Review 1981 (Box 73)
    - Trinitarian Bible Society (Box 73)
    - Trinity Broadcast Network (Box 73)
    - Triune Foundation (Box 73)
    - Gary Trudeau (Box 73)
    - Ted Turner (Box 73)
    - UFO's, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - UFO's, "Messages of Deception. UFO Contacts and Cults," by Jacques Vallee (Box 73)
    - Unarius Foundation (Box 73)
    - "Unified Field Theory. Research Book. Using Subjective Response to PSI-Plasma for Analysis of Properties. Neutral Charge Plasma Fields," by J.G. Gallimore (Box 73)
    - Unicorn (Box 73)
    - Union Life (Box 73)
    - Unitarian Universalists (Box 73)
    - United Cable (Box 73)
    - United Church of Christ (Box 73)
    - United Methodist Church (Box 73)
    - United Nations (Box 74)
    - United Nations, "The Cult of the All-Seeing Eye," by Robert Keith Spenser (Box 74)
    - The United States (Box 74)
    - United World Colleges (Box 74)
    - Unity and Diversity World Organization (Box 74)
    - Unity Institute for Holistic Living, Detroit, MI. (Box 74)
    - Unity: Michigan Churches (Box 74)
    - Unity: Theology (incl. Unity School of Christianity) (Box 74)
    - Unity: Unity Village, MD. (incl. photographic slides) (Box 74)
    - The Universal House of Justice (Box 74)
    - The Universal Life Church (Box 74)
    - University of the Trees, Christopher Hills (Box 74)
    - Upland Hills, Ecological Center and Farm School (Box 74)
    - The Upsat Commission (Box 74)
    - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 74)
    - Utah (Box 74)
    - Utne Reader (Box 74)
    - Vail Institute (Box 74)
    - Values Clarification (incl. Project Charlie) (Box 74)
    - John Vasconcellos (Box 74)
    - Vatican II (Box 74)
    - Vatican Infiltration (Box 74)
    - Vedanta Press Books (Box 74)
    - Vegetarianism (Box 74)
    - Vietnam (Box 74)
    - Vineyard Ministries International (Box 74)
    - Virginia (Box 74)
    - Virgin Islands (Box 74)
    - Virgin Mary Apparitions (Box 74)
    - Visualization (Box 74)
    - Vitagenics Seminars (Box 74)
    - Kim Vogler (Box 74)
    - Harold Vogt, Ph.D. (Box 74)
    - Voodoo Cults (Box 75)
    - Mother Waddles (Box 75)
    - Dennis Waitley (Box 75)
    - Waldorf Institute (Rudolf Steiner) (Box 75)
    - War On Fundamentalism (Box 75)
    - Phyllis Warren (Box 75)
    - Washington, Church Council of Greater Seattle (Box 75)
    - Washington D.C., 3 folders (Box 75)
    - Washington for Jesus (Box 75)
    - George Washington (Box 75)
    - Washington, Seattle, 5 folders (Box 75)
    - Washington, State of, 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Washington Community Chapel and Bible Training Center (Box 76)
    - Water Baptism (Box 76)
    - The Way International (Box 76)
    - Wayne State University (Box 76)
    - Weapons Usage by New Agers (Box 76)
    - We Are The World (incl. book) (Box 76)
    - Nesta Webster (incl. "The Specialist Network," by Nesta Webster, 1926) (Box 76)
    - We Care Ministries (Box 76)
    - Weight Control Programs (Box 76)
    - Wellness (Box 76)
    - H.G. Wells (Box 76)
    - West Virginia (Box 76)
    - Paul Weyrich (Box 76)
    - White Eagle Lodge, "The Story of the White Eagle Lodge," 1986 (Box 76)
    - Rev. Terry Cole Whittaker (Box 76)
    - Whole Earth Catalog (Box 76)